Anastasia Yaskevich

Android Developer

Minsk, Belarus anastasia.yaskevich@gmail.com +375 (29) 352-69-32

SUMMARY

I am Android developer for more than 1 year and more than 4 years in software engineering in total. Worked both as solo developer and in a team, supported existing apps and created new ones from scratch. Also have remote work experience. Familiar with such tools as Jira, Git, Figma, Invision. English level is Intermediate+.

EDUCATION

09/2011 — 06/2016

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Specialist's Degree in Computer Systems and Networks. Got specialization of Sotfware for Information Technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2018 — 03/2019

Android Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile application. Used Kotlin, MVI, Clean Architecture, Retrofit, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, JUnit and Mockito for unit testing. Done part of performance optimization of UI. Worked in a team of 3 to 6 developers, 2 QA and 2 designers.

03/2018 — 11/2018

Android Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a client mobile application. Used Kotlin, Retrofit, Room, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, MVP, Clean Architecture. Took part in implementation of Form Decorator (transformed JSON of field appearance description into UI). Also implemented small demo app using same technologies. Worked in a team of 2 developers, 2 QA and a designer.

07/2016 — 03/2018

Frontend Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile web application on React.js and ES6, Redux. Refactoring and support of Android wrapper app on Crosswalk. Worked in a team of 8 developers, 4 QA and a designer.

11/2015 — 07/2016

Groovy Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a large betting web application. Used technologies: Groovy & Grails, MySQL, CoffeeScript, AngularJS, Redis. Also implemented CMS for that app. Worked in a team of 6 developers and 4 QA engineers.

02/2015 — *11/2015*

Junior Groovy Developer at REID Consulting

Creating small web applications from scratch. Used Groovy & Grails and Jenkins as CI. Also implemented all the frontend part. Worked alone but had code review by a mentor.